Tel. +972 54 5482798

boazlev@gmail.com

Skills

Experienced, highly skilled software engineer with proven capabilities in system analysis and development through the life-cycle of a product - gathering requirements, analyzing different solutions, design, implementation (independent and as part of a team), testing and quality assurance. Innovative and motivated to explore new technologies. Excellent ability to learn, system-wide understanding. Skills include:

- Pure Java development, OOD / OOP, Spring
- GUI (Swing) applications based on HMVC framework
- Test Drive Development (TDD) based on JUnit / JMock / Mockito
- EMF (Eclipse Modeling Framework)
- Eclipse IDE including knowledge in plugins development
- Tools: JTest, EclEmma, JRebel, Chronon, Code Collaborator, different profilers
- Operating systems: Windows, Linux / Ubuntu, Unix / Solaris
- Version Control Systems: ClearCase, SVN / Subversion, Git, Perforce
- Maven, including plugins development

Languages: Hebrew - Mother tongue, English - Fluent

Work Experience

2013 - RSA, The Security Division of EMC - Principal Software Engineer

- Adaptive Authentication supported development team of risk based authentication and fraud detection platform in the cloud (using Cassandra, MSSQL, Azure SQL and DWH), improved project's structure and modules, significantly improved build and release cycles collaborating with Release Engineering (RE) team
- Supported DevOps team, responsible for environments setups and tenants provisioning for production, User Acceptance Test (UAT), QE and scale in MS Azure, with Professional Services (PS) collaboration.
- Best innovative idea for redefining secured mobile payments

2011 - 2013: HP Software - Senior software engineer

- Analysis and development of Eclipse-based IDE for developing information gathering capabilities from different IT systems into a data warehouse for KPIs calculation.
- Designed, developed and supported server side components and architecture, based on Spring and XSLT.
- InnoBlast best innovation: embedding voice technologies within IT products

2005 – 2011: Cisco Systems, Inc.- Senior software engineer and technical team lead

Responsibilities include:

- Supporting geographically dispersed software engineering teams.
- Knowledge handoff to development, tier 4, customer support, sales and marketing teams throughout the world, using frontal and virtual presentations (WebEx).
- Expand and improve application capabilities, combined with responsibility for server-side components.
- Initiate, design, develop and assimilate debug and simulation tools, in order to improve product quality and reduce development time cycles.
- Developed SDK of drivers for Network Management System, including development tools and verification tools, based on Eclipse plugins.

2000 – 2005: Sheer Networks - Software Engineer (acquired by Cisco)

- Participated in building up a startup, from the early stages.
- Developed Network Management Systems (NMS) for Internet Service Providers (ISPs) from startup to a mature product.
- Focused on application layer including complex software frameworks.
- Integration with Tom Sawyer for graphs and data visualization
- Diagnosis and resolution of scale issues.

Education

BSc mathematics and computer science, Tel Aviv University, 1997

Courses: TDD, Extreme Java ,Design Patterns ,JavaScript ,Dojo ,Presentations ,GTD, Customer Facing,

CISSP

Army service

Man personnel officer (adjutant), Rank: lieutenant